sageintacct.com 2019-07-15

# Website Privacy Policy | Sage Intacct

Effective Date: November 8, 2017

This privacy statement describes how Sage Intacct, Inc. collects and uses the personal information you provide on our public website: www.sageintacct.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

For information on the use of information collected through the Sage Intacct Service, please see our product privacy policy located at https://www.sageintacct.com/privacy_policy_full.php. Sage Intacct participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. We are committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List at <https://www.privacyshield.gov/list>.

Sage Intacct is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. We comply with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, we are subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>. Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website at <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>, you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

### Information we collect and how we use it

We collect demographic and contact information, such as your name, title, company name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and professional association and certain firmographic company information, such as number of employees, or industry, from visitors who wish to receive information about Sage Intacct and its products and services. We use this information to provide you with information about the products and services that we provide and to send you information regarding Sage Intacct or its partners, such as newsletters, promotions, and events. If you no longer wish to receive these email communications you may follow the unsubscribe mechanism contained in each of the emails you receive.

### Sage Intacct advocates

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a colleague about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name, email address, and phone number. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Sage Intacct stores this information for tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at [privacypolicy@intacct.com](mailto:privacypolicy@intacct.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

### Service providers

We use other third parties such as an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf, teleconference services to provide you with webinars and demos, and a hosting service provider to host and provide our content. When you sign up to receive any of these services, we will share your personal information only as necessary with the third party solely for the purpose of providing that service.

We provide the information to our trusted distribution partners who work on behalf of or with Sage Intacct under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your information to help Sage Intacct communicate with you about offers from Sage Intacct and our partners. These companies do not have any independent right to share this information. If you would like to opt out of having your information shared with these third parties you may contact us at [privacypolicy@intacct.com](mailto:privacypolicy@intacct.com).

### Legal disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process, and when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

If Sage Intacct is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

### Access to personally identifiable information

Upon request we will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. If you wish to correct, update or request the deletion of personally identifiable information provided to us you may also contact us using the information below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as you remain identified as a potential customer or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations and to resolve disputes.

### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can contact us at [privacypolicy@intacct.com](mailto:privacypolicy@intacct.com).

Sage Intacct, our advertising partners, analytics, and service providers use cookies or similar tracking technologies. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies to improve our website and emails by seeing which areas and features are most popular, to count the number of computers accessing our website, to personalize and improve your experience, and to record your preferences. Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

### Log files

As is true of most websites, we use a third party tracking-utility partner to gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to analyze trends and to help us improve your experience on our website.

### Re-targeted advertising

Re-targeted advertising uses information collected on an individual's web browsing behavior such as the pages they have visited or the searches they have made. This information is then used to display ads. The information collected is only linked to an anonymous cookie ID (alphanumeric number); it does not include any information that could be linked back to a particular person, such as their name, address, or credit card number. The information used for targeted advertising either comes from Sage Intacct or through third party website publishers. If you would like to opt out of re-targeted advertising from Sage Intacct that occurs when visiting our third party advertising publishers, please click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/), or if located in the European Union, click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

### Links to other sites

Our Site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from those of Sage Intacct. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit.

### Testimonials

We post customer testimonials on our website which may contain personally identifiable information. We do obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial. If you wish to request the removal of your testimonial you may do so by contacting us at [privacypolicy@intacct.com](mailto:privacypolicy@intacct.com).

### Public forums

Our website offers publicly accessible blogs or community forums. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or community forum, contact us at [privacypolicy@intacct.com](mailto:privacypolicy@intacct.com). In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

### Social media widgets

Our website includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook button and Widgets, such as the Share this button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Changes to this policy

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### Contact us

You may direct questions regarding our website privacy policy to [privacypolicy@intacct.com](mailto:privacypolicy@intacct.com) or, by telephone, to Sage Intacct's customer support staff at 877-704-3700 or via postal mail at 300 Park Avenue, Suite 1400, San Jose, CA, 95110.
